chatovod.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy policy - Chatovod - create your chat!

#### Pricacy policy

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use the Chatovod service, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your email address.

**Data collection**  
To register for Chatovod, you are asked to provide your email address. You are also asked to choose a personal screen name and password. You may also provide optional information, such as your gender, country, zip code, age and photo. 

**Cookies**  
When you use Chatovod, a cookie and an Adobe Flash Shared Object are stored on your computer. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Adobe Flash Shared Object is a file written by the Adobe Flash Player to locally store your information, such as your login name. We use cookies and Flash Shared Objects to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Similarly, you can change the settings of your Adobe Flash player to reject Shared Objects. 

**IP addresses**  
We do store IP addresses of all incoming connections to Chatovod servers. This information is stored for security purposes such as preventing abuse or intrusion. When a user sends a message to a Chatovod Group, the IP address of the sender is recorded and displayed to the group owner and to the group moderators created by the group owner, so that the group owner and moderators can ban the sender from the group. IP addresses contain no personal or confidential information. 

**Payment Information**  
We store payment information (credit card type, card holder's name, credit card expiration date, PayPal account email) for all payments and donations made to Chatovod. Credit card numbers are not stored on our servers. This information is only used for security purposes, such as preventing fraudulent payments. 

**Information sharing**

  1. We do not sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals. We may share such information in the following limited circumstances: 
    1. We have your consent. 
    2. We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
    3. We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Chatovod, its users or the public. 
  2. If you choose to provide your age, gender, location, photographs or videos, we may share this information with other Chatovod users as a part of the Chatovod service. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**Information security**

  1. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We do not store your passwords, or credit card numbers, we only store their HMAC hash. 
  2. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

**Changes to this Policy** Please note this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Any new version or updates will be posted on this page. If you have any additional questions, please [contact us](http://help.chatovod.com/help/chats/new/). 

Jul 06, 2013
